Jenson, Vernon Additional Arbitration Files 5839
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Vernon Jenson Additional Arbitration Files
1945-1986
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Jensen, Vernon
5839
15 cubic feet
15 linear ft.
Records (documents).
5725206
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: /3002: Vernon H. Jensen Papers /4007: Vernon H. Jensen Additional Records /4067: Vernon H. Jensen Longshore Research Files /4096: Vernon H. Jensen Additional Research and Office Files /4128: Vernon H. Jensen Additional Papers /4128 AV: Vernon H. Jensen Audio-Visual Materials /4137: Vernon H. Jensen Additional Files 5739: Post Office Arbitration Files 5902: Vernon H. Jensen Additional Arbitration Files
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives 227 Ives Hall Tower Road Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheelref@cornell.edu https://catherwood.library.cornell.edu/kheel/
Compiled by:
A. Holland-Loucks, July 20, 2005
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, April 17, 2019
Machinists; Automobile industry and trade; Chemical workers; Electric power transmission; Metal trade; Metal workers -- Labor unions; Petroleum refineries; Textile industry; Textile workers -- Labor unions; Container industry; Paper products industry; Clerks -- Labor unions; Rubber industry and trade; Baked products industry; Coal mines and mining; Agricultural industries; Iron industry and trade; Iron industry and trade -- Employees; Communication and traffic; Hospitals -- Employees -- Labor unions; Municipal officials and employees -- Labor unions; Teachers' unions; Electricians -- Labor unions; Arbitration, Industrial; Truck drivers -- Labor unions; Absenteeism (Labor); Alcoholism and employment; Discrimination in employment; Wages; Contracting out; Labor unions; Applications for positions; Employee fringe benefits; Health insurance.; Grievance arbitration; Insubordination; Hours of labor; Promotions; Tardiness; Jensen, Vernon; Bell Aerosystems Company; Carborundum Company; Curtiss Wright Corporation; International Union, United Automobile, Aircraft, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America; Oil, Chemical, and Atomic Workers International Union; Service Employees International Union; Sperry Rand Corporation. Univac Division; State, County, and Municipal Workers of America; Trico Products Corporation; United Steelworkers of America
5725206
- AVX, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Acme Electric, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Aerofin, 1959-1961 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Air Products, 1962-1963 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Akron, 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Akron #2, 1978-1979 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Al Tech Specialty Steel, 1978-1980 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Al Tech Specialty Steel #2, 1978-1979 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Albany Felt, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Albany Steel, 1976-1977 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- All-Steel, 1976-1977 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Allied Chemical, 1974-1977 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Allied Chemical #2, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Amerace-Esna, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- American Bakeries Co., 1980 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- American Brass, 1957-1959 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- American Lafrance, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- American Lafrance #2, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- American Lafrance #3, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- American Lafrance #4, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- American Lafrance #5, 1980-1981 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- American Museum, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- American Sterilizer, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Anaconda, 1956-1976 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Anaconda #2, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Anaconda #3, 1978-1979 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Anaconda #4, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Anaconda #5, 1974-1982 (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Arcata, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Arcata #2, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Arcata #3, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Arcata #4, 1978-1979 (Box 1, Folder 32)
- Armstrong, 1956-1957 (Box 1, Folder 33)
- Armstrong #2, 1960-1962 (Box 1, Folder 34)
- Arvin, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 35)
- Arvin #2, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 36)
- Ashland, 1976-1977 (Box 1, Folder 37)
- Ashland #2, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 38)
- Ashland #3, 1980-1981 (Box 1, Folder 39)
- Badger, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Beechnut, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Beacon, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Beacon #2, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Beacon #3, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Bell Aerospace, 1964-1966 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Bell Aerospace #2, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Bell Aerosystems, 1964-1965 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Bell Aerosystems #2, 1962-1965 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Bell Aerosystems #3, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Bell Aerosystems #4, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Bell Aerosystems #5, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Bell Aerosystems #6, 1965-1968 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Bell Aerospace, 1977-1980 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Bell Aircraft, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Bethlehem, 1977-1978 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Bethlehem #2, 1970-1971 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Bethlehem #3, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Bethlehem #4, 1971-1977 (Box 2, Folder 19)
- Bethlehem #5, 1971-1980 (Box 2, Folder 20)
- Binghamton, 1976-1977 (Box 2, Folder 21)
- Blaw-Knox, 1958-1959 (Box 2, Folder 22)
- Blaw-Knox #2, 1956 (Box 2, Folder 23)
- Blaw-Knox #3, 1956 (Box 2, Folder 24)
- Blaw-Knox #4, 1956 (Box 2, Folder 25)
- Blaw-Knox #5, 1956 (Box 2, Folder 26)
- Bliss, 1962-1964 (Box 2, Folder 27)
- Bliss #2, 1962-1964 (Box 2, Folder 28)
- Borden, 1977-1978 (Box 2, Folder 29)
- Borden #2, 1980-1981 (Box 2, Folder 30)
- Boston, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 31)
- Brockway, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 32)
- Brunner, 1955-1957 (Box 2, Folder 33)
- Bucyrus, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 34)
- Buffalo Meter, 1964-1966 (Box 2, Folder 35)
- Buffalo Transit, 1951 (Box 2, Folder 36)
- Capital, 1979-1980 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Carborundum, 1956 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Carborundum #2, 1956 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Carborundum #3, 1958 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Carborundum #4, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Carborundum #5, 1956 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Carborundum #6, 1952-1957 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Carborundum #7, 1955 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Caterpillar, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Cayuga, 1980-1981 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Cerro, 1981-1983 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Cerro #2, 1980-1982 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Cheektowaga, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Children's, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Children's #2, 1966-1967 (Box 3, Folder 15)
- Cleveland Electric, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 16)
- Cleveland Electric #2, 1967-1970 (Box 3, Folder 17)
- Cleveland Pneumatic, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 18)
- Colorado Fuel, 1945-1946 (Box 3, Folder 19)
- Columbia Mills, 1958-1959 (Box 3, Folder 20)
- Columbia Mills #2, 1960-1962 (Box 3, Folder 21)
- Columbian Rope, 1951 (Box 3, Folder 22)
- Columbian Rope #2, 1952-1955 (Box 3, Folder 23)
- Community, 1977-1982 (Box 3, Folder 24)
- Continental Can, 1976-1977 (Box 3, Folder 25)
- Continental Can #2, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 26)
- Courier, 1976-1977 (Box 3, Folder 27)
- Crawford, 1961 (Box 3, Folder 28)
- Crown Zellerbach, 1980-1981 (Box 3, Folder 29)
- Cryovac, 1954-1957 (Box 3, Folder 30)
- Curtice, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 31)
- Curtiss, 1956 (Box 3, Folder 32)
- Curtiss #2, 1956 (Box 3, Folder 33)
- Curtiss #3, 1951-1959 (Box 3, Folder 34)
- Curtiss #4, 1961 (Box 3, Folder 35)
- Curtiss, 1961 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Curtiss #2, 1962 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Curtiss #3, 1961 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Curtiss #4, 1959-1963 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Curtiss #5, 1963 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Curtiss #6, 1962-1964 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Curtiss #7, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Curtiss #8, 1964-1965 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Curtiss #9, 1962-1965 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Curtiss #10, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Curtiss #11, 1965 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- Cyclotherm, 1949 (Box 4, Folder 12)
- Cyclotherm #2, 1958 (Box 4, Folder 13)
- Cyprus, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 14)
- Dayton, 1961-1962 (Box 4, Folder 15)
- Dayton #2, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 16)
- Dayton #3, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 17)
- Dietz, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 18)
- Dollinger, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 19)
- Dresser, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 20)
- Duffy, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 21)
- Dunlop, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 22)
- Eastern Metals, 1961 (Box 4, Folder 23)
- Eaton, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 24)
- Eaton #2, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 25)
- Eberle, 1963 (Box 4, Folder 26)
- Ellis, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 27)
- Elmira, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 28)
- Erie, 1976-1977 (Box 4, Folder 29)
- Ernest, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 30)
- Exolon, 1962-1964 (Box 4, Folder 31)
- Exolon #2, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 32)
- Fairbanks, 1959 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Fairport, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Federal Bearings, 1966 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Foster Bros., 1952 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Foster Wheeler, 1954 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Foster Wheeler #2, 1946-1953 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Foster Wheeler #3, 1965 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Foster Wheeler #4, 1965-1966 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- French, 1965 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- French #2, 1965 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- French #3, 1963-1964 (Box 5, Folder 11)
- Freinhofer's, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 12)
- General Products, 1964-1965 (Box 5, Folder 13)
- General Railway, 1976-1980 (Box 5, Folder 14)
- General Railway #2, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 15)
- General Telephone, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 16)
- Sylvania, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 17)
- Hamburg, 1975-1976 (Box 5, Folder 18)
- Harvard, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 19)
- Harvard #2, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 20)
- Hilliard, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 21)
- Hilliard #2, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 22)
- Hobart, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 23)
- Hooker, 1965 (Box 5, Folder 24)
- Hooker #2, 1974-1976 (Box 5, Folder 25)
- Imperial, 1959 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  Scope and Contents
  3 Photographs
- Imperial #2, 1959 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Ingersoll, 1976-1980 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Interstate, 1980-1981 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- East Irondequoit, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Johnson, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- K Poster, 1965 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Kay, 1965 (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Keith, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 9)
- Kenmore, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 10)
- Kennedy, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 11)
- Kennedy Valve, 1981-1983 (Box 6, Folder 12)
- Kimberly, 1954-1964 (Box 6, Folder 13)
- Kimberly #2, 1965 (Box 6, Folder 14)
- Kroehler, 1976-1977 (Box 6, Folder 15)
- Kroehler #2, 1979-1980 (Box 6, Folder 16)
- Label Processing Corp - IAM (International Association of Machinists), 1982-1983 (Box 6, Folder 17)
- Lindsay, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 18)
- Loblaw, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 19)
- Loblaw #2, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 20)
- Lux, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 21)
- McLean Thinking, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 22)
- MK, 1979-1982 (Box 6, Folder 23)
- MK #2, 1977-1981 (Box 6, Folder 24)
- Malecki, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 25)
- Marlin, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 26)
- Masonelian, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 27)
- Midstate, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 28)
- Midstate #2, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 29)
- Miller, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Miller #2, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Mohawk Valley Com. Col - MVCC, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 3)
- United Airlines, 1983-1985 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- United Airlines #2, 1981-1986 (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Monroe, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 6)
- Monroe #2, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 7)
- Monroe #3, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 8)
- Monticello, 1980-1981 (Box 7, Folder 9)
- Morse, 1963-1964 (Box 7, Folder 10)
- Morse #2, 1964 (Box 7, Folder 11)
- Movie, 1965 (Box 7, Folder 12)
- Muench, 1975-1978 (Box 7, Folder 13)
- Muench #2, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 14)
- NL, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 15)
- NL #2, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 16)
- National Biscuit, 1963 (Box 7, Folder 17)
- National Lead, 1963 (Box 7, Folder 18)
- National Lead, 1964 (Box 7, Folder 19)
- National Lead #2, 1963-1964 (Box 7, Folder 20)
- National Lead #3, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 21)
- Native, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 22)
- Nestle, 1962-1971 (Box 7, Folder 23)
- Nestle #2, 1976-1977 (Box 7, Folder 24)
- Nestle #3, 1978-1981 (Box 7, Folder 25)
- NJ Bell, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 26)
- NJ Bell #2, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 27)
- NJ Power, 1965-1966 (Box 7, Folder 28)
- NJ Power #2, 1963 (Box 7, Folder 29)
- NY Airbrake, 1958 (Box 7, Folder 30)
- NY Airbrake #2, 1959 (Box 7, Folder 31)
- NY Airbrake #3, 1959 (Box 7, Folder 32)
- NYSEG, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 33)
- NYSEG #2, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 34)
- NYS Office of General Services, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 35)
- Niagara, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Niagara #2, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 2)
- Niagara #3, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 3)
- Niagara #4, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 4)
- Niagara #5, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 5)
- Niagara #6, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 6)
- Nyack, 1973-1975 (Box 8, Folder 7)
- Olean, 1973-1974 (Box 8, Folder 8)
- Olin, 1972-1973 (Box 8, Folder 9)
- Onondaga, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 10)
- Otis, 1965 (Box 8, Folder 11)
- Otis #2, 1965 (Box 8, Folder 12)
- Otis #3, 1974-1975 (Box 8, Folder 13)
- Pan Am, 1963-1966 (Box 8, Folder 14)
- Pan Am #2, 1967 (Box 8, Folder 15)
- Pennsalt, 1961-1963 (Box 8, Folder 16)
- Penn Yan, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 17)
- Phillips, 1964 (Box 8, Folder 18)
- Portsmouth, 1969 (Box 8, Folder 19)
- Pratt, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 20)
- Process, 1975-1976 (Box 8, Folder 21)
- Process #2, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 22)
- Providence, 1972-1973 (Box 8, Folder 23)
- Public Service, 1965-1966 (Box 8, Folder 24)
- Public Service #2, 1964-1965 (Box 8, Folder 25)
- Pyron, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 26)
- Pyron #2, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 27)
- Quaker, 1963-1964 (Box 8, Folder 28)
- Rathbone, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 1)
- Reactive, 1967-1968 (Box 9, Folder 2)
- Reichhold, 1964 (Box 9, Folder 3)
- Remington, 1963 (Box 9, Folder 4)
- Remington #2, 1963 (Box 9, Folder 5)
- Remington #3, 1963 (Box 9, Folder 6)
- Remington #4, 1956-1963 (Box 9, Folder 7)
- Remington #5, 1965 (Box 9, Folder 8)
- Remington #6, 1963-1965 (Box 9, Folder 9)
- Remington #7, 1967 (Box 9, Folder 10)
- Resthaven, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 11)
- Revere, 1977-1978 (Box 9, Folder 12)
- Rhobbe, 1973 (Box 9, Folder 13)
- Richmondville, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 14)
- Robertshaw, 1979-1981 (Box 9, Folder 15)
- Robertson, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 16)
- Roblin, 1966 (Box 9, Folder 17)
- Rochester, City of, 1981 (Box 9, Folder 18)
- Rochester, City of #2, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 19)
- Rochester, City of #3, 1977-1978 (Box 9, Folder 20)
- Rochester, City of #4, 1970-1976 (Box 9, Folder 21)
- Rochester Folding, 1951 (Box 9, Folder 22)
- Rochester Steel, 1964 (Box 9, Folder 23)
- Rochester Telephone, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 24)
- Rochester Telephone, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 25)
- Rochester Telephone #2, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 26)
- Rochester Telephone #3, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 27)
- Rochester Telephone #4, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 28)
- Rochester Telephone #5, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 29)
- Rochester Telephone #6, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 30)
- Rochester Telephone #7, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 31)
- Rochester Telephone #8, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 32)
- Rochester Telephone #9, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 33)
- Rockwell, 1959-1961 (Box 9, Folder 34)
- Rockwell #2, 1961 (Box 9, Folder 35)
- Rockwell #3, 1963 (Box 9, Folder 36)
- Rockwell #4, 1972-1973 (Box 9, Folder 37)
- Rockwell #5, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 38)
- Rogers, 1958 (Box 9, Folder 39)
- Rollway, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 40)
- Rome, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 41)
- Rome #2, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 42)
- Rome #3, 1977-1979 (Box 9, Folder 43)
- Roosevelt, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 1)
- Rutland, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 2)
- St. Francis, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 3)
- St. Francis #2, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 4)
- St. Francis #3, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 5)
- St. Joe, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 6)
- St. Joseph, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 7)
- St. Joe #2, 1974-1975 (Box 10, Folder 8)
- St. Joseph #2, 1954-1956 (Box 10, Folder 9)
- St. joseph #3, 1954-1959 (Box 10, Folder 10)
- St. Joseph #4, 1962 (Box 10, Folder 11)
- St. Joseph #5, 1965 (Box 10, Folder 12)
- St. Joseph #6, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 13)
- St. Regis, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 14)
- St. Regis #2, 1976 (Box 10, Folder 15)
- Schenectady, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 16)
- Schoeller, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 17)
- Schweizer, 1969-1971 (Box 10, Folder 18)
- Schweizer #2, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 19)
- Scott, 1966-1968 (Box 10, Folder 20)
- Scovill, 1970 (Box 10, Folder 21)
- Scovill #2, 1970 (Box 10, Folder 22)
- Scovill #3, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 23)
- Scovill #4, 1973 (Box 10, Folder 24)
- Scranton, 1968 (Box 10, Folder 25)
- South Seneca, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 26)
- Shenendehowa, 1982 (Box 10, Folder 27)
- Shenendehowa #2, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 28)
- Shepard, 1974-1975 (Box 10, Folder 29)
- Shepard #2, 1974-1975 (Box 10, Folder 30)
- Shuron, 1966 (Box 10, Folder 31)
- Shuron #2, 1967 (Box 10, Folder 32)
- Shuron #3, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 33)
- Simonds, 1972-1974 (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Simonds #2, 1976-1977 (Box 11, Folder 2)
- Simonds #3, 1975-1976 (Box 11, Folder 3)
- Simonds #4, 1975-1976 (Box 11, Folder 4)
- Smith, 1965 (Box 11, Folder 5)
- Smith #2, 1965 (Box 11, Folder 6)
- Smith #3, 1965 (Box 11, Folder 7)
- Smith #4, 1965 (Box 11, Folder 8)
- Smith #5, 1961-1965 (Box 11, Folder 9)
- Speer, 1966-1968 (Box 11, Folder 10)
- Sportservice, 1967 (Box 11, Folder 11)
- Sportswear #2, 1967 (Box 11, Folder 12)
- Sportswear #3, 1962-1967 (Box 11, Folder 13)
- Stauffer, 1961-1972 (Box 11, Folder 14)
- Sterling, 1974-1980 (Box 11, Folder 15)
- Sterling #2, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 16)
- Stone, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 17)
- Strodel, 1968 (Box 11, Folder 18)
- Strodel #2, 1961-1963 (Box 11, Folder 19)
- Stromberg, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 20)
- Stuart, 1962 (Box 11, Folder 21)
- Sullivan, 1979 (Box 11, Folder 22)
- Sullivan Community General Hospital - 1199, 1983 (Box 11, Folder 23)
- Sun, 1964-1965 (Box 11, Folder 24)
- Symington, 1962 (Box 11, Folder 25)
- Tek, 1969 (Box 12, Folder 1)
- Telescope, 1969 (Box 12, Folder 2)
- Textron, 1976 (Box 12, Folder 3)
- Textron #2, 1976 (Box 12, Folder 4)
- Textron #3, 1976 (Box 12, Folder 5)
- Tioga, 1980-1981 (Box 12, Folder 6)
- Tompkins, 1981-1982 (Box 12, Folder 7)
- Tompkins #2, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 8)
- Toms, 1971 (Box 12, Folder 9)
- Torrington, 1971-1972 (Box 12, Folder 10)
- Torrington, 1971 (Box 12, Folder 11)
- Torrington #3, 1971-1972 (Box 12, Folder 12)
- Torrington #4, 1977 (Box 12, Folder 13)
- Torrington #5, 1977 (Box 12, Folder 14)
- Trane, 1965 (Box 12, Folder 15)
- Trico, 1967 (Box 12, Folder 16)
- Trico #2, 1967 (Box 12, Folder 17)
- Trico #3, 1967 (Box 12, Folder 18)
- Trico #4, 1967-1968 (Box 12, Folder 19)
- Trico #5, 1965 (Box 12, Folder 20)
- Trico #6, 1969 (Box 12, Folder 21)
- Trico #7, 1969 (Box 12, Folder 22)
- Trico #8, 1969 (Box 12, Folder 23)
- Trico #9, 1968 (Box 12, Folder 24)
- Trico #10, 1968-1970 (Box 12, Folder 25)
- Trico #11, 1970 (Box 12, Folder 26)
- Trico #12, 1967-1969 (Box 12, Folder 27)
- Trico #13, 1970 (Box 12, Folder 28)
- Trico #14, 1970 (Box 12, Folder 29)
- Trico #15, 1968-1970 (Box 12, Folder 30)
- Trico #16, 1968-1971 (Box 12, Folder 31)
  2 Photographs
- Trico #17, 1971 (Box 12, Folder 32)
- Trico #18, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 33)
- Trico #19, 1970-1971 (Box 12, Folder 34)
- Trico #20, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 35)
- Trico #21, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 36)
- Trico #22, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 37)
- Trico #23, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 38)
- Trico #24, 1972 (Box 13, Folder 1)
- Trico #25, 1972 (Box 13, Folder 2)
- Trico #26, 1969-1971 (Box 13, Folder 3)
- Trico #27, 1971 (Box 13, Folder 4)
- Trico #28, 1972-1973 (Box 13, Folder 5)
- Trico #29, 1974 (Box 13, Folder 6)
- Trico #30, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 7)
- Trico #31, 1971 (Box 13, Folder 8)
- Trico #32, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 9)
- Trico #33, 1974 (Box 13, Folder 10)
- Trico #34, 1974 (Box 13, Folder 11)
- Trico #35, 1973-1975 (Box 13, Folder 12)
- Trico #36, 1974-1975 (Box 13, Folder 13)
- Trico #37, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 14)
- Trico #38, 1977 (Box 13, Folder 15)
- Trico #39, 1976 (Box 13, Folder 16)
- Trico #40, 1976-1977 (Box 13, Folder 17)
- Trico #41, 1975-1976 (Box 13, Folder 18)
- Trico #42, 1976 (Box 13, Folder 19)
- Trico #43, 1978 (Box 13, Folder 20)
- Trico #44, 198 (Box 13, Folder 21)
- Trico #45, 1977-1978 (Box 13, Folder 22)
- Trico #46, 1977-1978 (Box 13, Folder 23)
- Trico #47, 1977-1978 (Box 13, Folder 24)
- Trico #48, 1977-1978 (Box 13, Folder 25)
- Triumph, 1981 (Box 13, Folder 26)
- True, 1981 (Box 13, Folder 27)
- True, 1980 (Box 13, Folder 28)
- UMC, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 1)
- UMC #2, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 2)
- US Air Force, 1976 (Box 14, Folder 3)
- US Air Force #2, 1976 (Box 14, Folder 4)
- US Air Force #3, 1978 (Box 14, Folder 5)
- US Air Force #4, 1978 (Box 14, Folder 6)
- US Air Force #5, 1976-1977 (Box 14, Folder 7)
- US Air Force #6, 1975-1977 (Box 14, Folder 8)
- US Air Force #7, 1977-1979 (Box 14, Folder 9)
- US Air Force #8, 1973-1979 (Box 14, Folder 10)
- US Social, 1977 (Box 14, Folder 11)
- US Trucking, 1966 (Box 14, Folder 12)
- United Whelan, 1964 (Box 14, Folder 13)
- Univac, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 14)
- Univac #2, 1968-1969 (Box 14, Folder 15)
- Univac #3, 1970 (Box 14, Folder 16)
- Univac #4, 1969-1970 (Box 14, Folder 17)
- Univac #5, 1971 (Box 14, Folder 18)
- Univac #6, 1972-1973 (Box 14, Folder 19)
- Univac #7, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 20)
- Univac #8, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 21)
- Univac #9, 1974-1976 (Box 14, Folder 22)
- Univac #10, 1976 (Box 14, Folder 23)
- VAW, 1978-1979 (Box 14, Folder 24)
- Vanchlor, 1979 (Box 14, Folder 25)
- Varcum, 1967 (Box 14, Folder 26)
- Varcum #2, 1969-1970 (Box 14, Folder 27)
- Varcum #3, 1971 (Box 14, Folder 28)
- Varcum #4, 1965-1970 (Box 14, Folder 29)
- Varcum #5, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 30)
- Varcum #6, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 31)
- Varcum #7, 1976 (Box 14, Folder 32)
- Vega, 1970-1971 (Box 14, Folder 33)
- Vulcan, 1973-1974 (Box 14, Folder 34)
- WIXT, 1976-1978 (Box 15, Folder 1)
- Ward, 1964 (Box 15, Folder 2)
- Watervliet, 1977-1979 (Box 15, Folder 3)
- Watervliet #2, 1970-1979 (Box 15, Folder 4)
- Western Electric, 1975-1978 (Box 15, Folder 5)
- Western Electric #2, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 6)
- Western Electric #3, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 7)
- Western Electric #4, 1974-1975 (Box 15, Folder 8)
- Western Publishing, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 9)
- Western Publishing #2, 1979-1981 (Box 15, Folder 10)
- Western Publishing #3, 1978 (Box 15, Folder 11)
- Western Publishing #4, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 12)
- Westinghouse, 1964-1965 (Box 15, Folder 13)
- Westraco, 1977 (Box 15, Folder 14)
- Westraco #2, 1974-1977 (Box 15, Folder 15)
- West Virginia, 1965-1966 (Box 15, Folder 16)
- West Virginia #2, 1965-1966 (Box 15, Folder 17)
- Whitehaven, 1978 (Box 15, Folder 18)
- Whiting, 1969 (Box 15, Folder 19)
- Wilson, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 20)
- Wilson #2, 1972-1975 (Box 15, Folder 21)
- Winthrop, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 22)
- Worthington, 1962-1964 (Box 15, Folder 23)
- Worthington #2, 1981 (Box 15, Folder 24)
- Yale, 1968 (Box 15, Folder 25)
- Yale #2, 1969-1971 (Box 15, Folder 26)